

SOFTWARE ENGINEER STUDENT · DEVOPS ENTHUSIAS

Martin-Luther-ring 38, Schmalkalden, Thüringen , 98574, Germany

□ (+33) 751249206 | ☑ neji.said0@gmail.com | ☑ neji-glitch | 匝 neji-said-a415a513a/



"Whatever the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve."

Summary.

I am an enthusiastic software engineer student. With over two years of valuable experience in the IT industry, I've actively participated in the development, testing, deployment and maintenance of features for several software projects aimed at solving common real-world problems. I thrive in collaborative team settings where the exchange of knowledge and teamwork contribute to collective progress, ultimately benefiting the company and the customers. My passion for continuous learning drives me to enhance my skills, both on a personal and professional level. I'm eager to delve into emerging technologies and seize opportunities for personal and career growth.

Education

Schmalkalden university of applied sciences

MASTER EXCHANGE PROGRAM COMPUTER SCIENCE

Tek-up(Private College of Engineering and Technology)

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING DEGREE

Schmalkalden, Germany

Sep. 2022 - Sep. 2023

Ariana, Tunisia

Sep. 2020 - April. 2023

Certifications and Awards

2023 Coursera, IBM certification: Continous integration and continous delivery (CI/CD) from IBM

2023 Coursera, Continuous Delivery and DevOps from university of virginia

2023 British Council, British Council English certificate

2022 Google Digital Academy, Google Analytics Certification

2019 Finalist, hackathon "HACK FOR THE FUTURE"

Tunis city, Tunisia

Work Experiences_

Bestrade Company Ariana, Tunisia

FRONTEND DEVELOPER FREELANCER

Jun. 2021 - Jan. 2022

- · Create, test, debug, document, and implement new features for a collaborative platform dedicated to international trade professionals.
- Work directly with the Product Manager, and suggest new features and improvements to current ones.
- Maintain and add new features to our UI component Library and Modules.
- Using devops best practices and automate the integration, the build and testing through CI/CD pipelines
- Languages: HTML, Javascript, Typescript, CSS
- Technologies/ keywords: React js, Redux, Nextjs, rxjs, MVC, Tailwindcss, Nodejs, mogodb, Git, Jasmine, Github, Microservices, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Github actions, Docker

Mediterranean Store Company

Ariana, Tunisia

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER FREELANCER

Dec. 2019 - dec. 2020

- · Create, build, test, and implement and deploy new features for a responsive e-commerce site for the sale of organic and artisanal products.
- Support in Creating, building and integrating API to access the application data.
- Manipulate and control data to meet necessary conditions throughout the entire data lifecycle.
- Set, plan and implement social media and communication campaigns and strategies.
- Languages: HTML, Javascript, Typescript, CSS, PHP
- Technologies/ keywords: Vanillajs, bootstrap, Mysql, Karma, Git, Gitlab, bash, illustrator, Marketing, UI/UX

IT Consult and Integration

Ben Arous, Tunisia

Intern Software engineer Dec. 2018 - May. 2019

- · Create, build and test features of an an android application designed to protect users from traffic risks.
- Collect data and construct a dataset related to previous road accidents.
- Train and build a machine learning model to estimate the probability of user's accident rate based on real-time data.
- Transform the machine learning model into an API and Integrate it with the android application.
- Implementing Push Notifications With Google Cloud Messaging
- Languages: Java, Python
- Technologies/ keywords: Android studio, Tensorflow, Pandas, Flask, nodeJs, Socket.io, mongoDB, expressJS, Firebase.



Programming Languages, C/C++, Java, Javascript, Python, PHP, CSS, HTML

Frameworks, Reacjs, Nodejs, Angular, Django, symphony, Flask, Tensorflow, pandas, Nextjs, Bootstrap, Tailwindcss

Cloud Services, Amazon web services, Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud Platform

Test and build Tools, Jasmine, Karma, nose, Eslint, pylint, Flake8, selenuim, Cucumber, TestNg, Buildah, Maven, Gradle

Architectures, MVC, MVVM, MVP

 $\textbf{Integration, Automation and cloud tools}, \ \mathsf{Devops, Jenkins, Git, Github, Gitlab, Circle CI, Github \ \mathsf{actions, Integration}, \ \mathsf{Github, Gitlab, Circle CI, Github \ actions}, \ \mathsf{Github, Gi$

Tekton, Kubernetes, Ansible, Terraform, Docker, Docker Hub, Tekton Hub, Bash scripting, Vagrant

Monitoring and management tools, Jira, Kibana, Grafana, Confluence, Trello

Operating systems, Linux, Centos, Ubuntu, Android, Windows

Software Methodologies, Agile Scrum, Cycle V, Waterfall

Network and communication protocols, HTTP, FTP, DNS, SSH, SMTP, TCP/IP, UDP Websockets, VoIP

Languages

English, Fluent (B2: British council English certificate)

French, Fluent (TCF C1)

German, Basic

Arabic, Native